Guide to the North Carolina State University, Athletics, Media Relations Records
North Carolina State University, Athletics, Media Relations Records
- Football, 1895-2007; 1895 2007; In 1892, the first official football game at NC State was played against a local prep school, Raleigh Male Academy; in 1893, State played their first intercollegiate game against Tennessee. The 1895 team was the first to wear the now traditional red and white colore
  - NC State vs. Maryland: program, 17 Nov. 2001 (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - Media guide, Spring 2004 (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - Media guide, 2005 (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - Wolfpack Preview program (NC State vs. Virginia Tech), 4 Sept. 2005 (Box 273, Folder 16)
  - Wolfpack Preview program (NC State vs. Eastern Kentucky), 17 Sept. 2005 (Box 275, Folder 1)
  - Wolfpack Preview program (NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill), 24 Sept. 2005 (Box 275, Folder 2)
  - Wolfpack Preview program (NC State vs. Clemson), 13 Oct. 2005 (Box 275, Folder 3)
  - Wolfpack Preview program (NC State vs. Southern Mississippi), 29 Oct. 2005 (Box 275, Folder 4)
  - Wolfpack Preview program (NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State), 19 Nov. 2005 (Box 275, Folder 5)
  - Wolfpack Preview program (NC State vs. Maryland), 26 Nov. 2005 (Box 275, Folder 6)
  - Wolfpack Preview program (NC State vs. Boston College), 23 Sept. 2006 (Box 275, Folder 7)
  - Wolfpack Preview program (NC State vs. Florida State), 5 Oct. 2006 (Box 275, Folder 8)
  - Wolfpack Preview program (NC State vs. Wake Forest), 14 Oct. 2006 (Box 275, Folder 9)
  - Wolfpack Preview program (NC State vs. Georgia Tech), 4 Nov. 2006 (Box 275, Folder 10)
  - Wolfpack Gameday program (NC State vs. Clemson), 22 Sept. 2007 (Box 275, Folder 11)
  - Wolfpack Game Day program (NC State vs. Virginia), 27 Oct. 2007 (Box 275, Folder 12)
  - Athletic Camp flyer, undated (Box 173, Folder 10)
  - Depth charts, undated (Legalbox 206, Folder 3)
  - Football candidate form, undated (Box 173, Folder 11)
  - "No Ordinary Joe: NC State's Joe McIntosh" poster, undated (Flatfolder 1)
  - Questionnaires, undated (Legalbox 206, Folder 4)
  - Ticket information, undated (Box 173, Folder 12)
  - Varsity letter award, undated (Box 173, Folder 13)
- Men's Golf, 1930-1987, 1998; 1930 1998; The first Men's Golf team was organized in 1930, but it wasn’t until 1934 that NC State began sponsering golf as a varsity sport. Coach Richard Sykes, who was hired in 1972, remains the coach of the team as of 2009, and is the athletics department’s longest-serving employee. Coach Sykes has won four ACC Coach of the Year awards, produced five ACC Tournament individual champions, one ACC Play of the Year, two ACC Rookies of the Year, 28 All-Americas and more than 40 All-ACC selections.
  This series contains records from the Men's Golf teams, including clippings, media guides, game programs, game and player statistics, press releases, rosters, schedules, player questionnaires, brochures, media guides, and other publications and general information. Materials are arranged chronologically by season.
  - History, 1930-1949 (Box 221, Folder 11)
  - Scores, 1952 (Box 221, Folder 12)
  - General information, 1957 (Box 221, Folder 13)
  - Schedule, 1959 (Box 221, Folder 14)
  - General information, 1960 (Box 221, Folder 15)
  - General information, 1961 (Box 221, Folder 16)
  - General information, 1962 (Box 221, Folder 17)
  - General information, 1963 (Box 221, Folder 18)
  - General information, 1964 (Box 221, Folder 19)
  - General information, 1965 (Box 221, Folder 20)
  - General information, 1966 (Box 221, Folder 21)
  - General information, 1967 (Box 221, Folder 22)
  - General information, 1968 (Box 222, Folder 1)
  - General information, 1969 (Box 222, Folder 2)
  - General information, 1969-1970 (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - General information, 1970-1971 (Box 222, Folder 4)
  - General information, 1971-1972 (Box 222, Folder 5)
  - General information, 1972-1973 (Box 222, Folder 6)
  - General information, 1973-1974 (Box 222, Folder 7)
  - Questionnaires, 1973-1974 (Box 222, Folder 8)
  - General information, 1974-1975 (Box 222, Folder 9)
  - General information, 1975-1976 (Box 223, Folder 1)
  - Media guide, 1976 (Box 223, Folder 2)
  - General information, 1976-1977 (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Media guide, 1977 (Box 223, Folder 4)
  - General information, 1977-1978 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Media guide, 1978 (Box 223, Folder 6)
  - General information, 1978-1979 (Box 223, Folder 7)
  - Media guide, 1978-1979 (Box 223, Folder 8)
  - General information, 1979-1980 (Box 223, Folder 9)
  - Media guide, 1979-1980 (Box 223, Folder 10)
  - General information, 1980-1981 (Box 223, Folder 11)
  - Media guide, 1980-1981 (Box 223, Folder 12)
  - General information, 1981-1982 (Box 224, Folder 1)
  - Media guide, 1981-1982 (Box 224, Folder 2)
  - General information, 1982-1983 (Box 224, Folder 3)
  - General information, 1983-1984 (Box 224, Folder 4)
  - General information, 1984-1985 (Box 224, Folder 5)
  - General information, 1985-1986 (Box 224, Folder 6)
  - General information, 1986-1987 (Box 224, Folder 7)
  - General Information, 1988-1989 (Box 277, Folder 4)
  - Schedule Poster (1998-1999 season), 1998 1998 (Oversizeflatbox 274, Folder 3)
- Men's Gymnastics, 1976-1986; 1976 1986; The Men's Gymnastics team was grated varsity status in 1975, and remained active until 1986, when the Men's Gymnastics program was eliminated.
  This series contains records from the Men's Gymnastics teams, including clippings, media guides, event information, statistics, press releases, rosters, schedules, player questionnaires, brochures, and other publications and general information. Materials are arranged chronologically by season.
  - General information, 1976-1977 (Box 225, Folder 1)
  - Questionnaires, 1977-1978 (Box 225, Folder 2)
  - General information, 1978-1979 (Box 225, Folder 3)
  - General information, 1979-1980 (Box 225, Folder 4)
  - General information, 1980-1981 (Box 225, Folder 5)
  - General information, 1981-1982 (Box 225, Folder 6)
  - General information, 1982-1983 (Box 225, Folder 7)
  - General information, 1983-1984 (Box 225, Folder 8)
  - General information, 1984-1985 (Box 225, Folder 9)
  - General information, 1985-1986 (Box 225, Folder 10)
  - Media guide, 1986 (Box 225, Folder 11)
  - Cancellation of Men's Gymnastics program (article), 25 Jun. 1986 (Box 225, Folder 12)
- Men's Lacrosse, 1972-1985; 1972 1985; The Men's Lacrosse team was granted varsity status in 1972, and remained at that level into the early 1980s. By the mid-1980s, the Men's Lacrosse varsity program had been eliminated and lacrosse became a club sport at NC State.
  This series contains records from the Men's Lacrosse teams, including clippings, media guides, event information, statistics, press releases, rosters, schedules, player questionnaires, brochures, and other publications and general information. Materials are arranged chronologically by season, with general, season-long records coming before files from individual events (where present).
  - General information, 1972 (Box 226, Folder 1)
  - General information, 1973 (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - General information, 1973-1978 (Legalbox 214, Folder 11)
  - Pamphlet, 1973 (Box 226, Folder 3)
  - General information, 1974 (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - General information, 1975 (Box 226, Folder 5)
  - Pamphlet, 1975 (Box 226, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Washington & Lee: program, 20 Apr. 1975 (Box 226, Folder 7)
  - General information, 1976 (Box 226, Folder 8)
  - Pamphlet, 1976 (Box 226, Folder 9)
  - General information, 1977 (Box 226, Folder 10)
  - Pamphlet, 1977 (Box 226, Folder 11)
  - General information, 1978 (Box 226, Folder 12)
  - Pamphlet, 1978 (Box 226, Folder 13)
  - General information, 1979 (Box 226, Folder 14)
  - Pamphlet, 1979 (Box 227, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Johns Hopkins (NCAA Division I Lacrosse Championship Tournament), 16 May 1979 (Box 227, Folder 2)
  - General information, 1980 (Box 227, Folder 3)
  - General information, 1980-1981 (Box 227, Folder 4)
  - Pamphlet, 1980 (Box 227, Folder 5)
  - North-South All-Star Lacrosse Game (39th Annual), 14 Jun. 1980 (Box 227, Folder 6)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Lacrosse Guide, 1981 (Box 227, Folder 7)
  - General information, 1981 (Box 227, Folder 8)
  - Pamphlet, 1981 (Box 227, Folder 9)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Lacrosse Handbook, 1982 (Box 227, Folder 10)
  - General information, 1982 (Box 227, Folder 11)
  - Pamphlet, 1982 (Box 227, Folder 12)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: program, 27 Mar. 1982 (Box 227, Folder 13)
  - Wolpack Lacrosse: A Brief History From 1972 Through 1985 (Box 227, Folder 14)
- Men's Rifle, 1961-1982; 1961 1982; Men’s Rifle became a varisty sport in 1958. As a part of the South Eastern Air Rifle Conference (SEARC), the team won their first conference title in 2003-04. In 2006-07, the team joined the Great American Rifle Conference, a top national rifling conference.
  This series contains records from the Men's Rifle teams, including clippings, media guides, event information, statistics, press releases, rosters, schedules, player questionnaires, brochures, and other publications and general information. Materials are arranged chronologically by season.
  - General information, 1961-1965 (Box 227, Folder 15)
  - Clippings, 1966-1968 (Box 227, Folder 16)
  - General information, 1966-1967 (Box 227, Folder 17)
  - General information, 1967-1968 (Box 227, Folder 18)
  - General information, 1968-1969 (Box 227, Folder 19)
  - General information, 1969-1970 (Box 227, Folder 20)
  - General information, 1970-1971 (Box 227, Folder 21)
  - General information, 1971-1972 (Box 227, Folder 22)
  - General information, 1972-1973 (Box 227, Folder 23)
  - General information, 1973-1974 (Box 227, Folder 24)
  - General information, 1975-1976 (Box 227, Folder 25)
  - General information, 1977-1978 (Box 227, Folder 26)
  - General information, 1978-1979 (Box 227, Folder 27)
  - General information, 1979-1980 (Box 227, Folder 28)
  - Schedule, 1981-1982 (Box 227, Folder 29)
- Men's Soccer, 1955-2001; 1955 2001; Although it was unofficially organized two years early, Men's Soccer became a varsity sport in 1949. Benito Artinatos became the first All-American in soccer at NC State during two consecutive years, 1962 and 1963. In 1990, the team won their first ACC championship.
  This series contains records from the Men's Soccer teams, including clippings, media guides, game information, statistics, press releases, rosters, schedules, player questionnaires, brochures, and other publications and general information. Materials are arranged chronologically by season.
  - General information, 1955 (Box 227, Folder 30)
  - General information, 1956 (Box 227, Folder 31)
  - Award for Varsity Monogram (letter), 1956 (Legalbox 214, Folder 12)
  - General information, 1957 (Box 227, Folder 32)
  - General information, 1958 (Box 228, Folder 1)
  - General information, 1959 (Box 228, Folder 2)
  - General information, 1960 (Box 228, Folder 3)
  - General information, 1961 (Box 228, Folder 4)
  - General information, 1962 (Box 228, Folder 5)
  - General information, 1963 (Box 228, Folder 6)
  - General information, 1964 (Box 228, Folder 7)
  - General information, 1965 (Box 228, Folder 8)
  - General information, 1966 (Box 228, Folder 9)
  - General information, 1967 (Box 228, Folder 10)
  - General information, 1968 (Box 228, Folder 11)
  - General information, 1969 (Box 228, Folder 12)
  - General information, 1970 (Box 228, Folder 13)
  - Media guide, 1970 (Box 228, Folder 14)
  - General information, 1971 (Box 228, Folder 15)
  - General information, 1972 (Box 228, Folder 16)
  - General information, 1973 (Box 228, Folder 17)
  - General information, 1974 (Box 228, Folder 18)
  - General information, 1975 (Box 229, Folder 1)
  - General information, 1976 (Box 229, Folder 2)
  - General information, 1977 (Box 229, Folder 3)
  - Slides, 1977 (Box 229, Folder 4)
  - General information, 1978 (Box 229, Folder 5)
  - Pamphlet, 1978 (Box 229, Folder 6)
  - General information, 1979 (Box 229, Folder 7)
  - Pamphlet, 1979 (Box 229, Folder 8)
  - General information, 1980 (Box 229, Folder 9)
  - General information, 1980-1982 (Box 229, Folder 10)
  - Pamphlet, 1980 (Box 230, Folder 1)
  - Wolfpack Soccer Camp, Jun. - Jul. 1980 (Box 230, Folder 2)
  - Pamphlet, 1981 (Box 230, Folder 3)
  - Wolfpack Soccer Camp, Jun. 1981 (Box 230, Folder 4)
  - General information, 1982-1983 (Box 230, Folder 5)
  - Pamphlet, 1982 (Box 230, Folder 6)
  - Wolfpack Soccer Camp, Jun. 1982 (Box 230, Folder 7)
  - Pamphlet, 1984 (Box 230, Folder 8)
  - Wolfpack Soccer Day Camp, Jun., Aug. 1991 (Box 230, Folder 9)
  - NC State Soccer School, Jul. 1991 (Box 230, Folder 10)
  - NC State Wolfpack Soccer Camp, 27 Jul. - 1 Aug. 1991 (Box 230, Folder 11)
  - NC State Soccer School, 1992 (Box 230, Folder 12)
  - Media guide, 2000 (Box 230, Folder 13)
  - Media guide, 2001 (Box 230, Folder 14)
- Men's Swimming and Diving, 1955-1990; 1955 1990; In 1946, Willis Casey was hired to coach Men's Swimming and Diving, and over the next thirty years, the team won or shared sixteen Southern Conference and Atlantic Coast Conference (ACC) championships. Bob Mattson became NC State's first NCAA champion in the 200-yard breaststroke in 1955. In 1954, the team won the Men’s Outdoor National AAU Championship. After 22 seasons, Casey stepped down as head coach to become Atheletic Director, putting Don Easterling in charge. During Easterling's tenure, the men won the ACC championship 12 consecutive times, 1966-82.
  This series contains records from the Men's Swimming and Diving teams, including clippings, media guides, meet information, statistics, press releases, rosters, schedules, player questionnaires, brochures, and other publications and general information. Materials are arranged chronologically by season.
  - General information, 1955-1956 (Box 230, Folder 15)
  - General information, 1956-1957 (Box 230, Folder 16)
  - Schedule, 1957-1958 (Box 230, Folder 17)
  - National Collegiate Swimming Championships (36th Annual), 26-28 Mar. 1959 (Box 230, Folder 18)
  - General information, 1959-1960 (Box 230, Folder 19)
  - General information, 1960-1961 (Box 230, Folder 20)
  - Eastern Intercollegiate Swimming League Individual Championships (21st Annual), 9-11 Mar. 1961 (Legalbox 214, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, 1961-1962 (Box 230, Folder 21)
  - General information, 1961-1962 (Box 230, Folder 22)
  - Questionnaires, 1961-1962 (Box 230, Folder 23)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Swimming and Diving Championships, 22-24 Feb. 1962 (Box 230, Folder 24)
  - Eastern Intercollegiate Swimming League Championships (22nd Annual), 15-17 Mar. 1962 (Legalbox 214, Folder 14)
  - NCAA Swimming Championships (39th Annual), 29-31 Mar. 1962 (Legalbox 214, Folder 15)
  - Men's Senior National AAU Indoor Swimming and Diving Championships, 5-7 Apr. 1962 (Box 231, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Invitational Long Course Age Group Swimming Championships (7th Annual), 6-7 Jul. 1962 (Legalbox 214, Folder 16)
  - Men's National AAU Outdoor Swimming Championships, 10-12 Aug. 1962 (Box 231, Folder 2)
  - Clippings (1 of 2), 1962-1963 (Box 231, Folder 3)
  - Clippings (2 of 2), 1962-1963 (Box 231, Folder 4)
  - General information, 1962-1963 (Box 231, Folder 5)
  - Media guide, 1962-1963 (Box 231, Folder 6)
  - Meets and results, 1962-1963 (Box 231, Folder 7)
  - Questionnaires, 1962-1963 (Box 231, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1963-1964 (Box 232, Folder 1)
  - General information, 1963-1964 (Box 232, Folder 2)
  - Meets and results, 1963-1964 (Box 232, Folder 3)
  - Questionnaires, 1963-1964 (Box 232, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1964-1965 (Box 232, Folder 5)
  - General information, 1964-1965 (Box 232, Folder 6)
  - Media guide, 1964-1965 (Box 232, Folder 7)
  - Meets and results, 1964-1965 (Box 232, Folder 8)
  - Questionnaires, 1964-1965 (Box 232, Folder 9)
  - Senior National A.A.U. Swimming Championships, 1-3 Apr. 1965 (Legalbox 214, Folder 17)
  - Foreign swimming choaches visit to NC State, Jul. 1965 (Box 232, Folder 10)
  - General information, 1965-1966 (Box 232, Folder 11)
  - Media guide, 1965-1966 (Box 232, Folder 12)
  - Questionnaires, 1965-1966 (Box 232, Folder 13)
  - Media guide, 1966-1967 (Box 232, Folder 14)
  - General information (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 232, Folder 15)
  - General information (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 233, Folder 1)
  - General information, 1968-1969 (Box 233, Folder 2)
  - Media guide, 1968-1969 (Box 233, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1969-1970 (Box 233, Folder 4)
  - General information, 1969-1970 (Box 233, Folder 5)
  - Media guide, 1969-1970 (Box 233, Folder 8)
  - Meets and results, 1969-1970 (Box 233, Folder 6)
  - Questionnaires, 1969-1970 (Box 233, Folder 7)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Swimming Championships, 26-28 Feb. 1970 (Box 233, Folder 9)
  - Eastern Intercollegiate Invitation Swimming Meet (13th Annual), 12-14 Mar. 1970 (Box 233, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1970-1971 (Legalbox 239, Folder 1)
  - General information, 1970-1971 (Box 233, Folder 11)
  - Media guide, 1970-1971 (Box 233, Folder 12)
  - Men's Swimming and Diving press releases, 1971 (Box 233, Folder 13)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Swimming Championships (18th Annual), 25-27 Feb. 1971 (Legalbox 239, Folder 2)
  - Eastern Intercollegiate Swimming League Invitation Meet (31st Annual), 11-13 Mar. 1971 (Box 233, Folder 14)
  - Clippings, 1971-1972 (Box 233, Folder 15)
  - General information, 1971-1972 (Box 233, Folder 16)
  - Media guide, 1971-1972 (Box 233, Folder 17)
  - Meets and results, 1971-1972 (Legalbox 239, Folder 3)
  - Men's Swimming and Diving press releases, 1971-1972 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - Questionnaires, 1971-1972 (Box 234, Folder 2)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Swimming and Diving Championships, 2-4 Mar. 1972 (Box 234, Folder 3)
  - NCAA Swimming and Diving Championships (49th Annual), 23-25 Mar. 1972 (Box 234, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1972-1973 (Box 234, Folder 5)
  - General information, 1972-1973 (Box 234, Folder 6)
  - Media guide, 1972-1973 (Box 234, Folder 7)
  - Meets and results, 1972-1973 (Legalbox 239, Folder 4)
  - Men's Swimming and Diving press releases, 1972-1973 (Box 234, Folder 8)
  - Outlook, 1972 (Legalbox 239, Folder 5)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Swimming and Diving Championships (21st Annual), 1-3 Mar. 1973 (Box 234, Folder 9)
  - Eastern Seaboard Intercollegiate Swimming and Diving Championships (33rd Annual), 8-10 Mar. 1973 (Box 234, Folder 10)
  - NCAA Swimming and Diving Championships (50th Annual), 22-24 Mar. 1973 (Legalbox 239, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1973-1974 (Box 234, Folder 11)
  - General information, 1973-1974 (Box 234, Folder 12)
  - Media guide, 1973-1974 (Box 234, Folder 13)
  - Meets and results, 1973-1974 (Legalbox 239, Folder 7)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Swimming and Diving Championships (21st Annual), 28 Feb. - 2 Mar. 1974 (Box 235, Folder 15)
  - NCAA Swimming and Diving Championships (51st Annual), 28-30 Mar. 1974 (Box 234, Folder 14)
  - Clippings, 1974-1975 (Box 234, Folder 15)
  - General information, 1974-1975 (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Media guide, 1974-1975 (Box 235, Folder 2)
  - Meets and results, 1974-1975 (Legalbox 239, Folder 8)
  - Men's Swimming and Diving press releases, 1974-1975 (Box 235, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, 1974-1975 (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Swimming and Diving Championships, 27 Feb. - 1 Mar. 1975 (Box 235, Folder 5)
  - Eastern Seaboard Swimming and Diving Championships, 6-8 Mar. 1975 (Box 235, Folder 6)
  - NCAA Swimming and Diving Championships (52nd Annual), 26-29 Mar. 1975 (Box 235, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1975-1976 (Box 235, Folder 8)
  - General information, 1975-1976 (Box 235, Folder 9)
  - Media guide, 1975-1976 (Box 235, Folder 10)
  - Meets and results, 1975-1976 (Legalbox 239, Folder 9)
  - Men's Swimming and Diving press releases, 1975-1976 (Box 235, Folder 11)
  - National AAU and Olympic results packets, 1976 (Box 235, Folder 12)
  - Photograph, 1975-1976 (Box 235, Folder 13)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Swimming and Diving Championships, 26-28 Feb. 1976 (Box 235, Folder 14)
  - Clippings, 1976-1977 (Box 235, Folder 16)
  - General information, 1976-1977 (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - Media guide, 1976-1977 (Box 236, Folder 2)
  - Meets and results, 1976-1977 (Box 236, Folder 3)
  - Men's Swimming and Diving press releases, 1976-1977 (Box 236, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, 1976-1977 (Box 236, Folder 5)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Swimming and Diving Championships, 24-26 Feb. 1977 (Box 236, Folder 6)
  - NCAA Swimming and Diving Championships (54th Annual), 24-26 Mar. 1977 (Box 236, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 236, Folder 8)
  - General information, 1977-1978 (Box 236, Folder 9)
  - Media guide, 1977-1978 (Box 236, Folder 10)
  - Meets and results, 1977-1978 (Box 236, Folder 11)
  - NCAA Swimming and Diving Championships (55th Annual), 23-25 Mar. 1978 (Box 236, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1978-1979 (Box 236, Folder 13)
  - General information, 1978-1979 (Box 236, Folder 14)
  - Media guide, 1978-1979 (Box 236, Folder 15)
  - Meets and results, 1978-1979 (Box 236, Folder 16)
  - Photographic negatives, 1978-1979 (Box 236, Folder 17)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Swimming and Diving Championships, 22-24 Feb. 1979 (Box 236, Folder 18)
  - NCAA Swimming and Diving Championships (56th Annual), 22-24 Mar. 1979 (Box 236, Folder 19)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference meets, 1979-1980 (Box 236, Folder 20)
  - Clippings, 1979-1980 (Box 237, Folder 1)
  - General information (1 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 237, Folder 2)
  - General information (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 237, Folder 3)
  - Media guide, 1979-1980 (Box 237, Folder 4)
  - Meets and results, 1979-1980 (Box 237, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters, 1979-1980 (Box 237, Folder 6)
  - Photographic negatives, 1979-1980 (Box 237, Folder 7)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Swimming and Diving Championships (27th Annual), 21-23 Feb. 1980 (Box 237, Folder 8)
  - NCAA Swimming and Diving Championships (57th Annual), 27-29 Mar. 1980 (Box 237, Folder 9)
  - Wolfpack Swimming Camp Incorporated, Jun. - Aug. 1980 (Box 237, Folder 10)
  - General information, 1980-1981 (Box 237, Folder 11)
  - Media guide, 1980-1981 (Box 237, Folder 12)
  - Wolfpack Swimming Camp Incorporated, Jun. - Aug. 1981 (Box 237, Folder 13)
  - General information, 1981-1982 (Box 237, Folder 14)
  - Media guide, 1981-1982 (Box 237, Folder 15)
  - Results, 1981-1983 (Box 238, Folder 1)
  - Wolfpack Swimming Camp Incorporated, Jun. - Jul. 1982 (Box 238, Folder 2)
  - Brochure, 1982-1983 (Box 238, Folder 3)
  - General information, 1982-1983 (Box 238, Folder 4)
  - General information, 1983-1984 (Box 238, Folder 5)
  - Schedule, 1989-1990 (Box 238, Folder 6)
  - Forms and policies, undated (Box 238, Folder 7)
  - Swim Coaching tape group, undated (Box 238, Folder 8)
- Men's Tennis, 1941-1985; 1941 1985; The Men's Tennis team began in 1954, under head coach Jack Kenfield. John Sadri was the first player to earn All-American honors in 1977, and advanced to the quaterfinals in the NCAA tournament that year. In 1978, Sadri competed in the NCAA finals against John McEnroe. In 1998, Roberto Bracone was named the Atlantic Coast Conference Player of the Year, the only NC State Men’s Tennis player in school history to win the award. In 2004, the J.W. Isenhour tennis facility opened.
  This series contains records from the Men's Tennis teams, including clippings, media guides, match information, statistics, press releases, rosters, schedules, player questionnaires, brochures, and other publications and general information. Materials are arranged chronologically by season.
  - Results, 1941 (Box 238, Folder 9)
  - General information, 1946 (Box 238, Folder 10)
  - General information, 1947 (Box 238, Folder 11)
  - General information, 1948 (Box 238, Folder 12)
  - General information, 1949 (Box 238, Folder 13)